## Chun Kiu Chan

Student

Email: chanchunkiu@hotmail.com
Phone: 080- 7653-6638
Date of birth: 2001-10-01
Nationality: Hong Kong

**PROFILE** 

As an enthusiastic university student, I am actively seeking employment opportunities that align with my interest. Over the past four years, I have been studying computer science and developed a comprehensive understanding of programming and its various applications.

**EXPERIENCE** 

Japan

Mar 2023 - Mar 2023

japan Jul 2022 - Sep 2022 **Teaching Assistant** 

University of Aizu

Provided guidance and assistance to students in the programming workshop

Internship

axrossroad

Contributed to the company's cryptocurrency research efforts, further refining my skills in Japanese reading and presentation. Acquired knowledge of NFT and cryptocurrency during the process.

**EDUCATION** 

Fukushima,Japan 2019 - Present Computer Science
University of Aizu

**SKILLS** 

• Problem-Solving

• Teamwork

· Handling conflict

**LANGUAGES** 

Cantonese Native

**Japanese** Advanced. N1

English Advanced

**Mandarin** Intermediate

**CERTIFICATIONS & COURSES** 

Udemy: Complete Blender Creator: Learn 3D Modelling for Beginners

Udemy: Complete Python Developer in 2023: Zero to Mastery